<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<excuses>
<excuse>
    <destination>Marshall</destination>
    <line>Geelong</line>
    <status>delayed for approximately 5 hours</status>
    <text>because drop bears have attacked the train driver near Little River. Got to watch those drop bears!</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Southern Cross</destination>
    <line>Geelong</line>
    <status>delayed for what seems like an eternity</status>
    <text>because those pesky signals at Newport are playing up again. You know, the ones that have been problematic for five years.</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Marshall</destination>
    <line>Geelong</line>
    <status>cancelled</status>
    <text>because the conductor didn't get his donut this morning.</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Warrnambool</destination>
    <line>Geelong</line>
    <status>delayed </status>
    <text>because it's hotter than 25 degrees, and the tracks aren't designed for Aussie summers. You know, where temperatures peak at 45 degrees...</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Southern Cross</destination>
    <line>Ballarat</line>
    <status>delayed for 30 minutes</status>
    <text>because a heatwave has caused the conductor to take an extra stop at the Ballan station in order to run to the supermarket to get another bottle of water. Services on the train such as lighting will continue to operate as they will leave the keys in the train while gone.</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Kyneton</destination>
    <line>Bendigo</line>
    <status>delayed for a mathematically indefinite period</status>
    <text>because timetables cannot be held as accurate during Dirac field type equivalence, Empty Eigenvector probability events and or strange entanglement. The next train to depart is the 9:ψλλ..ħ</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
    <destination>Bendigo</destination>
    <line>Bendigo</line>
    <status>replaced with road coaches</status>
    <text>because we didn't order enough spare rolling stock to cover when engines and carriages needed repairs</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
	<destination>Melton</destination>
	<line>Bacchus Marsh</line>
	<status>delayed until the train is feeling better</status>
	<text>because the train went out last ight and got very drunk, and is now hung over</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
	<destination>Wendouree</destination>
	<line>Ballarat<line>
	<status>replaced by road coaches</status>
	<text>because there are snails on the track ad we need to pop out to Bunnings to get some snail bait</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
	<destination>Malmsbury</destination>
	<line>Bendigo</line>
	<status>will be 30 minutes lates boarding</status>
	<text>because we cannot remember where we left the carriages. They're around here somewhere!</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
	<destination>Sale</destination>
	<line>Bairnsdale</line>
	<status>delayed for much longer than we advertise</status>
	<text>because an army of subversive beavers are building a dam. Across the tracks. In Australia. Where there are no beavers</text>
</excuse>
<excuse>
	<destination>Southern Cross</destination>
	<line>Geelong</line>
	<status>held indefinitely at the station without air conditioning or lights</status>
	<text>because the driver locked the keys to the cabin. Inside the cabin. </text>

</excuse>
</excuses>
